<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Stellar Horizon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellar Horizon]]></description><link>https://www.stellarhorizon.in/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:44:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.stellarhorizon.in/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[         Mahindra teases Thar.e concept, reveal on August 15]]></title><description><![CDATA[Unleashing the Future of Off-Roading: The Mahindra Thar.e EV Concept Buckle up, adventure enthusiasts and eco-conscious explorers,...]]></description><link>https://www.stellarhorizon.in/post/mahindra-teases-thar-e-concept-reveal-on-august-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64f3680afc5f70a3894c95c4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 16:57:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/659744_8d073fc817034b5c8032ca2909ef0d71~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Amith M</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Unleashing the Future of Off-Roading: The Mahindra Thar.e EV Concept</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Buckle up, adventure enthusiasts and eco-conscious explorers, because Mahindra is about to electrify the off-road world with its all-new Thar EV concept! With a teaser that&apos;s ignited excitement across the globe, the stage is set for the Thar.e to make its grand entrance in South Africa on August 15.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/659744_8d073fc817034b5c8032ca2909ef0d71~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p><strong>The Thar.e: A Name Worth the Wait</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As the tantalizing teaser suggests, the electric off-roader will proudly bear the name &quot;Thar.e.&quot; It&apos;s a name that resonates with rugged enthusiasts and symbolizes the evolution of an off-roading legend into the electric age.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But a name is just the beginning of the journey. The real thrill lies in what the Thar.e promises to bring to the table, and the teaser offers some enticing hints.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Squircle Magic and Pixel Perfection: The Design Unveiled</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Picture this: Squircle design elements adorning the LED lights of the Thar.e, giving it an unmistakable identity. These intriguing lights also sport a pixel structure, reminiscent of another exciting concept from Mahindra, a pickup truck that&apos;s set to dazzle at the event.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/659744_767e7e26f0eb44b780f1582d28136e7f~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p><br /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The Thar.e&apos;s design seems to bridge the gap between the rugged allure of its predecessor and a modern, futuristic aesthetic, promising an off-roading experience like no other.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Born Electric: A Revelation of the Platform</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">A phrase that has the automotive world buzzing - &quot;Born Electric.&quot; This isn&apos;t just a catchy slogan; it&apos;s a revelation. It hints at a groundbreaking move by Mahindra to craft the Thar.e on a brand-new, dedicated EV platform. This decision sends a clear message that Mahindra is ready to take the electric off-roading world by storm.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Weightless Wonder: Overcoming Challenges</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Electrifying a ladder-frame platform isn&apos;t a task for the faint of heart. Yet, Mahindra, with its extensive experience as a commercial vehicle manufacturer, has been quietly exploring this terrain. However, the Thar.e stands apart.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">By choosing to harness the potential of the &quot;born-electric&quot; platform, Mahindra sidesteps the weight and space constraints that the current Thar&apos;s ladder-frame structure would present. This means a Thar.e that&apos;s lighter on its feet, boasting more room for batteries, and potentially delivering an enviable range.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/659744_5ef1961628c9482399d79a7611f1817f~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p><strong>The Mystery Unveiled: What Lies Under the Hood</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The Thar.e&apos;s electrifying secrets are still tightly under wraps. Details about its range and powertrain remain elusive, leaving us in eager anticipation. But one thing&apos;s for sure: Mahindra is determined to rewrite the off-roading rulebook, and the Thar.e promises to be a game-changer in the world of electric adventure.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">So, whether you&apos;re a seasoned off-road warrior or a nature enthusiast looking to explore the wilds in style, the Thar.e is poised to offer an electrifying journey like no other. Stay tuned for more updates as we count down to the Thar.e&apos;s global debut on August 15 - a date that marks the dawn of a new era in off-roading excellence. Mahindra is ready to unleash the future, and it&apos;s a ride you won&apos;t want to miss!</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><br /></p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>